{"correct_answer": [0.373, 0.56], "wrong_answers": [[0.648, 0.972], [-0.065, -0.098], [0.156, 0.234], [0.076, 0.114]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_2_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_2_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.427, 0.64], "wrong_answers": [[1.163, 1.745], [0.086, 0.129], [1.275, 1.912], [0.798, 1.197]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_5_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_5_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.462, 0.693], "wrong_answers": [[0.014, 0.02], [-0.277, -0.415], [1.057, 1.585], [1.055, 1.583]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_6_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_6_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.32, 0.48], "wrong_answers": [[-0.322, -0.482], [0.183, 0.274], [-0.192, -0.289], [-0.371, -0.557]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_7_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_7_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.249, 0.373], "wrong_answers": [[0.589, 0.883], [0.753, 1.129], [0.111, 0.167], [-0.172, -0.258]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_7_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_7_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.462, 0.693], "wrong_answers": [[-0.087, -0.131], [0.248, 0.372], [0.753, 1.129], [0.996, 1.494]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_7_iris.csv_['petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_7_iris.csv_['petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.32, 0.48], "wrong_answers": [[-0.008, -0.013], [0.939, 1.408], [0.589, 0.884], [0.946, 1.419]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_8_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_8_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.444, 0.667], "wrong_answers": [[0.011, 0.016], [0.033, 0.05], [0.706, 1.059], [1.215, 1.822]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_10_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_10_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.16, 0.24], "wrong_answers": [[-0.485, -0.727], [0.475, 0.713], [0.361, 0.541], [0.549, 0.824]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_16_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_16_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.48, 0.72], "wrong_answers": [[-0.074, -0.11], [0.172, 0.258], [1.14, 1.709], [0.924, 1.387]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_17_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_17_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.142, 0.213], "wrong_answers": [[0.272, 0.408], [0.078, 0.118], [0.429, 0.644], [0.439, 0.659]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_21_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_21_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.48, 0.72], "wrong_answers": [[0.301, 0.451], [0.319, 0.478], [0.942, 1.413], [0.926, 1.389]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_22_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_22_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.462, 0.693], "wrong_answers": [[-0.571, -0.856], [0.931, 1.397], [0.77, 1.155], [0.764, 1.145]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_22_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_22_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.284, 0.427], "wrong_answers": [[0.808, 1.212], [0.066, 0.098], [0.066, 0.099], [-0.528, -0.792]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_23_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_23_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.196, 0.293], "wrong_answers": [[0.413, 0.62], [1.453, 2.18], [0.557, 0.836], [0.383, 0.575]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_25_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_25_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.373, 0.56], "wrong_answers": [[0.133, 0.199], [0.837, 1.256], [1.633, 2.45], [0.574, 0.86]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_27_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_27_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.622, 0.933], "wrong_answers": [[1.577, 2.366], [1.121, 1.682], [1.21, 1.815], [1.229, 1.844]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_29_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_29_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.302, 0.453], "wrong_answers": [[0.685, 1.028], [-0.305, -0.458], [0.646, 0.97], [0.667, 1.0]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_33_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_33_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.213, 0.32], "wrong_answers": [[1.025, 1.537], [0.381, 0.572], [0.786, 1.179], [0.344, 0.516]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_33_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_33_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.284, 0.427], "wrong_answers": [[0.69, 1.036], [0.096, 0.145], [0.463, 0.695], [0.153, 0.229]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_34_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_34_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.302, 0.453], "wrong_answers": [[0.152, 0.229], [0.109, 0.163], [0.536, 0.804], [1.183, 1.775]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_39_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_39_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.267, 0.4], "wrong_answers": [[1.388, 2.082], [-0.238, -0.358], [0.544, 0.817], [-0.108, -0.163]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_40_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_40_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.533, 0.8], "wrong_answers": [[0.909, 1.363], [0.255, 0.383], [-0.02, -0.03], [0.942, 1.413]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_41_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_41_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.533, 0.8], "wrong_answers": [[0.911, 1.366], [0.334, 0.5], [1.099, 1.649], [0.227, 0.34]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_41_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_41_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.551, 0.827], "wrong_answers": [[1.159, 1.739], [0.884, 1.326], [0.956, 1.435], [0.908, 1.361]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_42_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_42_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.391, 0.587], "wrong_answers": [[-0.049, -0.074], [0.79, 1.186], [1.329, 1.993], [0.751, 1.126]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_44_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_44_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.302, 0.453], "wrong_answers": [[0.864, 1.296], [-0.352, -0.528], [0.81, 1.215], [0.123, 0.185]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_46_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_46_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.373, 0.56], "wrong_answers": [[0.961, 1.441], [0.032, 0.048], [1.234, 1.851], [0.179, 0.269]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_49_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_49_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.267, 0.4], "wrong_answers": [[-0.208, -0.312], [0.135, 0.203], [0.117, 0.176], [0.77, 1.155]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_49_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_49_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.302, 0.453], "wrong_answers": [[1.005, 1.507], [0.585, 0.877], [1.455, 2.183], [0.556, 0.834]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_55_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_55_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.249, 0.373], "wrong_answers": [[0.927, 1.39], [0.878, 1.317], [0.836, 1.254], [0.542, 0.813]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_56_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_56_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.338, 0.507], "wrong_answers": [[0.943, 1.415], [0.585, 0.877], [0.67, 1.005], [0.643, 0.964]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_59_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_59_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.284, 0.427], "wrong_answers": [[0.485, 0.727], [0.009, 0.013], [0.8, 1.201], [0.066, 0.098]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_60_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_60_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.444, 0.667], "wrong_answers": [[1.037, 1.556], [0.068, 0.102], [0.845, 1.268], [1.005, 1.507]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_61_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_61_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.498, 0.747], "wrong_answers": [[0.132, 0.197], [0.296, 0.444], [0.774, 1.16], [0.767, 1.15]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_63_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_63_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.231, 0.347], "wrong_answers": [[-0.091, -0.137], [0.017, 0.025], [0.679, 1.019], [0.515, 0.772]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_65_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_65_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.356, 0.533], "wrong_answers": [[0.733, 1.1], [0.972, 1.458], [0.184, 0.276], [-0.081, -0.121]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_70_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_70_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.213, 0.32], "wrong_answers": [[0.892, 1.338], [0.874, 1.311], [-0.282, -0.423], [0.398, 0.598]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_71_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_71_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.409, 0.613], "wrong_answers": [[-0.358, -0.537], [1.026, 1.539], [0.755, 1.133], [0.747, 1.12]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_72_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_72_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.338, 0.507], "wrong_answers": [[0.01, 0.016], [0.01, 0.015], [0.041, 0.061], [0.809, 1.213]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_74_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_74_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.356, 0.533], "wrong_answers": [[1.052, 1.578], [0.828, 1.242], [0.818, 1.227], [0.801, 1.202]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_75_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_75_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.48, 0.72], "wrong_answers": [[1.193, 1.79], [0.912, 1.369], [0.807, 1.211], [1.062, 1.593]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_76_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_76_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.48, 0.72], "wrong_answers": [[0.165, 0.247], [0.225, 0.337], [0.148, 0.222], [1.028, 1.541]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_78_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_78_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.462, 0.693], "wrong_answers": [[1.205, 1.808], [-0.326, -0.488], [1.034, 1.551], [0.865, 1.297]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_79_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_79_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.338, 0.507], "wrong_answers": [[0.164, 0.246], [1.291, 1.936], [0.154, 0.23], [-0.447, -0.67]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_80_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_80_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.587, 0.88], "wrong_answers": [[1.534, 2.301], [0.991, 1.487], [1.388, 2.082], [0.012, 0.018]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_81_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_81_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.302, 0.453], "wrong_answers": [[-0.112, -0.167], [0.836, 1.255], [-0.231, -0.346], [-0.338, -0.507]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_87_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_87_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.32, 0.48], "wrong_answers": [[-0.072, -0.108], [0.088, 0.133], [0.559, 0.838], [0.624, 0.935]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_90_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_90_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.587, 0.88], "wrong_answers": [[0.326, 0.49], [0.908, 1.361], [0.313, 0.469], [1.214, 1.82]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_96_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_96_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.213, 0.32], "wrong_answers": [[0.691, 1.037], [-0.226, -0.339], [0.111, 0.167], [1.102, 1.653]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_99_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_99_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.249, 0.373], "wrong_answers": [[0.58, 0.871], [-0.124, -0.186], [0.797, 1.196], [0.837, 1.256]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_101_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_101_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.48, 0.72], "wrong_answers": [[0.91, 1.364], [0.798, 1.198], [-0.614, -0.921], [0.968, 1.452]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_101_iris.csv_['petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_101_iris.csv_['petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.284, 0.427], "wrong_answers": [[0.52, 0.779], [0.045, 0.067], [0.171, 0.257], [0.649, 0.973]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_104_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_104_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.249, 0.373], "wrong_answers": [[-0.117, -0.175], [0.518, 0.776], [-0.298, -0.447], [0.138, 0.207]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_107_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_107_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.391, 0.587], "wrong_answers": [[0.8, 1.201], [0.185, 0.277], [0.895, 1.342], [-0.615, -0.923]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_114_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_114_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.391, 0.587], "wrong_answers": [[0.169, 0.253], [0.118, 0.178], [1.042, 1.563], [-0.173, -0.26]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_117_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_117_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.302, 0.453], "wrong_answers": [[-0.05, -0.075], [-0.102, -0.152], [1.236, 1.854], [-0.589, -0.883]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_124_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_124_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.267, 0.4], "wrong_answers": [[1.071, 1.607], [0.48, 0.72], [0.487, 0.73], [0.425, 0.637]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_125_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_125_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.32, 0.48], "wrong_answers": [[0.53, 0.796], [0.005, 0.007], [1.271, 1.907], [0.49, 0.735]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_127_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_127_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.338, 0.507], "wrong_answers": [[0.645, 0.968], [-0.577, -0.865], [0.821, 1.231], [-0.464, -0.696]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_129_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_129_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.551, 0.827], "wrong_answers": [[0.237, 0.356], [0.353, 0.529], [0.333, 0.5], [-0.033, -0.05]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_133_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_133_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.196, 0.293], "wrong_answers": [[0.539, 0.808], [0.095, 0.143], [-0.373, -0.559], [0.103, 0.155]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_133_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_133_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.32, 0.48], "wrong_answers": [[-0.238, -0.357], [0.103, 0.155], [0.791, 1.187], [0.531, 0.797]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_135_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_135_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.249, 0.373], "wrong_answers": [[-0.014, -0.022], [0.102, 0.153], [0.5, 0.75], [0.711, 1.066]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_136_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_136_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.427, 0.64], "wrong_answers": [[0.209, 0.314], [0.264, 0.395], [-0.503, -0.755], [0.754, 1.131]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_142_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_142_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.373, 0.56], "wrong_answers": [[0.598, 0.897], [1.139, 1.709], [-0.117, -0.175], [0.789, 1.184]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_144_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_144_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.338, 0.507], "wrong_answers": [[0.693, 1.039], [0.865, 1.297], [-0.159, -0.238], [1.208, 1.812]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_146_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_146_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.32, 0.48], "wrong_answers": [[-0.269, -0.403], [0.559, 0.839], [0.076, 0.114], [0.808, 1.212]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_146_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_146_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.462, 0.693], "wrong_answers": [[0.709, 1.064], [1.05, 1.575], [-0.115, -0.173], [-0.068, -0.103]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_147_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_147_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.267, 0.4], "wrong_answers": [[0.731, 1.097], [0.57, 0.855], [0.437, 0.655], [0.48, 0.719]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_150_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_150_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.498, 0.747], "wrong_answers": [[0.034, 0.051], [0.272, 0.408], [-0.092, -0.138], [0.833, 1.249]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_154_iris.csv_['petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_154_iris.csv_['petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.213, 0.32], "wrong_answers": [[-0.139, -0.208], [0.686, 1.028], [0.423, 0.635], [-0.299, -0.449]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_159_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_159_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.498, 0.747], "wrong_answers": [[0.813, 1.219], [1.035, 1.553], [0.854, 1.28], [0.882, 1.324]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_159_iris.csv_['petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_159_iris.csv_['petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.267, 0.4], "wrong_answers": [[1.066, 1.599], [0.063, 0.095], [0.668, 1.002], [0.456, 0.684]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_161_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_161_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.391, 0.587], "wrong_answers": [[0.178, 0.267], [0.735, 1.103], [0.239, 0.358], [0.045, 0.067]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_162_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_162_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.373, 0.56], "wrong_answers": [[0.947, 1.42], [0.142, 0.213], [0.892, 1.337], [0.082, 0.122]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_163_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_163_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.267, 0.4], "wrong_answers": [[-0.242, -0.364], [0.635, 0.953], [-0.922, -1.384], [0.794, 1.191]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_163_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_163_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.444, 0.667], "wrong_answers": [[0.863, 1.294], [0.716, 1.075], [0.902, 1.352], [1.14, 1.71]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_167_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_167_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.462, 0.693], "wrong_answers": [[0.256, 0.384], [0.962, 1.443], [0.169, 0.254], [0.144, 0.216]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_169_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_169_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.302, 0.453], "wrong_answers": [[1.082, 1.623], [0.47, 0.704], [0.465, 0.697], [0.087, 0.13]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_171_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_171_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.302, 0.453], "wrong_answers": [[0.893, 1.34], [0.599, 0.899], [0.666, 0.999], [0.467, 0.7]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_173_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_173_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.48, 0.72], "wrong_answers": [[0.757, 1.135], [0.214, 0.321], [0.304, 0.456], [-0.058, -0.087]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_176_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_176_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.373, 0.56], "wrong_answers": [[0.749, 1.124], [0.562, 0.843], [0.165, 0.248], [-0.304, -0.456]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_177_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_177_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.391, 0.587], "wrong_answers": [[1.157, 1.736], [1.073, 1.609], [0.639, 0.959], [-0.09, -0.135]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_178_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_178_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.178, 0.267], "wrong_answers": [[0.11, 0.165], [0.0, 0.001], [-0.209, -0.314], [-0.065, -0.097]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_178_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_178_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.32, 0.48], "wrong_answers": [[-0.033, -0.05], [0.164, 0.246], [0.546, 0.82], [0.865, 1.297]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_179_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_179_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.32, 0.48], "wrong_answers": [[-0.004, -0.006], [0.635, 0.953], [1.315, 1.973], [-0.687, -1.031]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_181_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_181_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.587, 0.88], "wrong_answers": [[0.894, 1.341], [0.301, 0.451], [0.01, 0.015], [0.342, 0.513]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_183_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_183_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.444, 0.667], "wrong_answers": [[-0.306, -0.459], [0.178, 0.267], [-0.002, -0.004], [-0.037, -0.056]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_184_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_184_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.302, 0.453], "wrong_answers": [[0.967, 1.451], [0.72, 1.08], [-0.15, -0.225], [0.672, 1.008]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_185_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_185_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.444, 0.667], "wrong_answers": [[0.243, 0.365], [0.691, 1.037], [0.903, 1.355], [0.744, 1.116]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_191_iris.csv_['petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_191_iris.csv_['petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.267, 0.4], "wrong_answers": [[0.596, 0.894], [0.713, 1.069], [0.018, 0.028], [0.941, 1.411]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_192_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_192_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.516, 0.773], "wrong_answers": [[1.124, 1.686], [0.908, 1.363], [1.107, 1.66], [0.283, 0.425]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_193_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_193_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.249, 0.373], "wrong_answers": [[-0.196, -0.293], [-0.48, -0.72], [0.077, 0.116], [0.624, 0.937]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_194_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_194_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.302, 0.453], "wrong_answers": [[1.078, 1.617], [0.511, 0.766], [0.77, 1.155], [0.13, 0.196]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_195_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_195_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.249, 0.373], "wrong_answers": [[0.767, 1.15], [-0.333, -0.499], [-0.105, -0.157], [-0.052, -0.079]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_200_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_200_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.284, 0.427], "wrong_answers": [[0.055, 0.082], [0.059, 0.088], [0.606, 0.908], [-0.097, -0.145]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_200_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_200_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.32, 0.48], "wrong_answers": [[0.632, 0.948], [0.843, 1.264], [0.774, 1.161], [-0.067, -0.1]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_203_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_203_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.391, 0.587], "wrong_answers": [[0.595, 0.893], [0.218, 0.327], [0.74, 1.11], [0.209, 0.314]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_205_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_205_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.356, 0.533], "wrong_answers": [[1.116, 1.674], [1.161, 1.742], [0.21, 0.315], [0.08, 0.119]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_207_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_207_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.498, 0.747], "wrong_answers": [[-0.674, -1.011], [0.836, 1.255], [-0.169, -0.253], [1.09, 1.635]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_211_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_211_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.498, 0.747], "wrong_answers": [[0.152, 0.228], [-0.088, -0.132], [-0.017, -0.025], [0.259, 0.389]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_212_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_212_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.604, 0.907], "wrong_answers": [[-0.029, -0.043], [0.338, 0.507], [1.369, 2.053], [0.318, 0.477]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_213_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_213_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.338, 0.507], "wrong_answers": [[0.824, 1.236], [0.841, 1.262], [0.815, 1.222], [0.842, 1.263]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_213_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_213_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.231, 0.347], "wrong_answers": [[-0.261, -0.392], [0.052, 0.078], [0.062, 0.092], [0.763, 1.145]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_216_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_216_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.444, 0.667], "wrong_answers": [[0.158, 0.238], [-0.046, -0.069], [0.824, 1.236], [0.757, 1.136]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_216_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_216_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.551, 0.827], "wrong_answers": [[0.903, 1.354], [0.862, 1.293], [0.366, 0.55], [0.018, 0.027]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_216_iris.csv_['petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_216_iris.csv_['petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.213, 0.32], "wrong_answers": [[0.321, 0.482], [1.321, 1.981], [0.468, 0.702], [0.791, 1.186]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_218_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_218_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.249, 0.373], "wrong_answers": [[0.425, 0.638], [0.909, 1.364], [0.642, 0.963], [1.071, 1.607]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_225_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_225_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.32, 0.48], "wrong_answers": [[0.543, 0.814], [-0.23, -0.344], [0.638, 0.956], [-0.411, -0.616]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_231_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_231_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.498, 0.747], "wrong_answers": [[0.85, 1.275], [-0.486, -0.728], [0.786, 1.178], [1.101, 1.651]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_232_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_232_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.462, 0.693], "wrong_answers": [[1.213, 1.819], [0.983, 1.475], [0.984, 1.476], [1.005, 1.507]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_235_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_235_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.498, 0.747], "wrong_answers": [[-0.191, -0.287], [0.275, 0.412], [0.787, 1.18], [0.783, 1.174]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_236_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_236_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.32, 0.48], "wrong_answers": [[0.03, 0.045], [0.137, 0.205], [-0.031, -0.046], [-0.255, -0.383]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_237_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_237_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.213, 0.32], "wrong_answers": [[0.529, 0.793], [0.395, 0.592], [0.584, 0.876], [0.673, 1.01]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_238_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_238_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.213, 0.32], "wrong_answers": [[-0.077, -0.116], [0.396, 0.594], [0.616, 0.923], [0.706, 1.059]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_238_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_238_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.409, 0.613], "wrong_answers": [[-0.003, -0.004], [0.971, 1.456], [1.004, 1.507], [0.187, 0.28]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_239_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_239_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.338, 0.507], "wrong_answers": [[0.572, 0.858], [-0.03, -0.045], [-0.219, -0.328], [0.631, 0.946]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_241_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_241_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.516, 0.773], "wrong_answers": [[0.934, 1.401], [0.879, 1.318], [0.799, 1.199], [0.129, 0.194]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_242_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_242_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.516, 0.773], "wrong_answers": [[1.011, 1.516], [0.31, 0.465], [0.878, 1.317], [0.228, 0.342]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_243_iris.csv_['petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_243_iris.csv_['petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.124, 0.187], "wrong_answers": [[0.586, 0.879], [-0.185, -0.277], [0.249, 0.373], [-0.365, -0.547]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_252_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_252_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.284, 0.427], "wrong_answers": [[-0.742, -1.113], [0.444, 0.667], [-0.029, -0.043], [0.44, 0.661]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_255_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_255_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.444, 0.667], "wrong_answers": [[1.091, 1.637], [0.95, 1.425], [0.725, 1.088], [0.915, 1.373]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_256_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_256_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.249, 0.373], "wrong_answers": [[-0.038, -0.056], [0.864, 1.296], [0.584, 0.876], [0.424, 0.635]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_260_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_260_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.338, 0.507], "wrong_answers": [[0.185, 0.277], [0.982, 1.474], [0.908, 1.361], [0.87, 1.306]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_261_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_261_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.267, 0.4], "wrong_answers": [[0.988, 1.482], [1.152, 1.729], [0.003, 0.004], [0.505, 0.757]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_263_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_263_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.16, 0.24], "wrong_answers": [[-0.173, -0.26], [-0.332, -0.498], [-0.788, -1.182], [0.911, 1.366]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_267_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_267_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.178, 0.267], "wrong_answers": [[0.51, 0.765], [0.068, 0.102], [-0.268, -0.402], [0.993, 1.49]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_268_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_268_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.409, 0.613], "wrong_answers": [[0.141, 0.212], [1.171, 1.757], [1.114, 1.672], [-0.026, -0.039]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_269_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_269_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.498, 0.747], "wrong_answers": [[1.039, 1.559], [0.244, 0.366], [0.761, 1.142], [1.048, 1.572]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_273_iris.csv_['petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_273_iris.csv_['petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.356, 0.533], "wrong_answers": [[0.109, 0.164], [-0.275, -0.413], [-0.219, -0.328], [-0.179, -0.268]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_276_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_276_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.533, 0.8], "wrong_answers": [[1.038, 1.558], [-0.051, -0.076], [0.177, 0.266], [0.248, 0.372]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_276_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_276_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.302, 0.453], "wrong_answers": [[0.856, 1.284], [0.017, 0.025], [0.17, 0.255], [0.73, 1.095]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_278_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_278_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.302, 0.453], "wrong_answers": [[-0.304, -0.456], [0.572, 0.858], [-0.475, -0.712], [-0.131, -0.197]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_278_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_278_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.516, 0.773], "wrong_answers": [[1.136, 1.703], [0.777, 1.165], [-0.271, -0.407], [0.065, 0.097]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_280_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_280_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.302, 0.453], "wrong_answers": [[0.774, 1.161], [0.712, 1.068], [0.552, 0.828], [0.186, 0.278]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_282_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_282_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.462, 0.693], "wrong_answers": [[0.062, 0.092], [0.198, 0.297], [1.448, 2.172], [0.26, 0.391]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_282_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_282_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.267, 0.4], "wrong_answers": [[1.198, 1.797], [0.81, 1.215], [0.522, 0.782], [0.412, 0.618]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_282_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_282_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.32, 0.48], "wrong_answers": [[-0.099, -0.148], [-0.246, -0.369], [0.149, 0.224], [0.734, 1.101]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_286_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_286_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.231, 0.347], "wrong_answers": [[0.127, 0.19], [0.4, 0.6], [1.078, 1.617], [-0.099, -0.148]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_290_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_290_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.32, 0.48], "wrong_answers": [[0.538, 0.807], [0.68, 1.02], [-0.007, -0.011], [0.766, 1.149]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_290_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_290_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.373, 0.56], "wrong_answers": [[-0.1, -0.15], [0.562, 0.844], [0.689, 1.034], [0.596, 0.895]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_291_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_291_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.231, 0.347], "wrong_answers": [[0.689, 1.033], [-0.498, -0.746], [1.085, 1.627], [0.638, 0.957]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_292_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_292_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.373, 0.56], "wrong_answers": [[1.053, 1.58], [0.88, 1.319], [0.568, 0.852], [0.74, 1.11]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_293_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_293_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.444, 0.667], "wrong_answers": [[1.078, 1.617], [0.145, 0.218], [-0.068, -0.102], [1.217, 1.825]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_296_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_296_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.391, 0.587], "wrong_answers": [[0.759, 1.138], [0.123, 0.185], [-0.051, -0.076], [-0.075, -0.113]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_300_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_300_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.32, 0.48], "wrong_answers": [[0.514, 0.771], [0.532, 0.799], [0.699, 1.048], [0.576, 0.863]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_301_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_301_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.32, 0.48], "wrong_answers": [[1.331, 1.997], [0.1, 0.149], [0.771, 1.157], [0.537, 0.806]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_302_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_302_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.356, 0.533], "wrong_answers": [[0.569, 0.853], [1.247, 1.871], [0.825, 1.237], [0.19, 0.285]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_304_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_304_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.409, 0.613], "wrong_answers": [[1.082, 1.623], [1.133, 1.7], [0.685, 1.027], [-0.323, -0.484]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_306_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_306_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.373, 0.56], "wrong_answers": [[0.813, 1.219], [0.642, 0.963], [1.599, 2.398], [1.168, 1.752]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_308_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_308_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.409, 0.613], "wrong_answers": [[0.713, 1.07], [0.122, 0.183], [0.726, 1.09], [1.077, 1.616]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_308_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_308_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.267, 0.4], "wrong_answers": [[-0.183, -0.274], [0.718, 1.077], [0.065, 0.097], [0.081, 0.122]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_311_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_311_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.498, 0.747], "wrong_answers": [[-0.062, -0.093], [0.98, 1.47], [0.266, 0.4], [0.202, 0.303]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_311_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_311_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.462, 0.693], "wrong_answers": [[1.072, 1.609], [0.229, 0.343], [0.989, 1.483], [1.033, 1.549]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_320_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_320_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.373, 0.56], "wrong_answers": [[0.901, 1.352], [1.587, 2.38], [0.09, 0.135], [0.872, 1.307]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_323_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_323_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.533, 0.8], "wrong_answers": [[0.16, 0.24], [0.3, 0.45], [0.961, 1.442], [-0.276, -0.414]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_324_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_324_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.249, 0.373], "wrong_answers": [[-0.163, -0.245], [0.621, 0.932], [0.057, 0.086], [1.095, 1.642]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_325_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_325_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.249, 0.373], "wrong_answers": [[0.507, 0.76], [0.039, 0.058], [0.063, 0.095], [-0.471, -0.707]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_325_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_325_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.302, 0.453], "wrong_answers": [[0.73, 1.096], [0.683, 1.025], [0.564, 0.847], [0.907, 1.36]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_331_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_331_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.178, 0.267], "wrong_answers": [[-0.253, -0.379], [-0.344, -0.517], [0.649, 0.974], [0.039, 0.059]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_335_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_335_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.249, 0.373], "wrong_answers": [[-0.051, -0.077], [0.079, 0.118], [-0.226, -0.34], [0.457, 0.686]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_335_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_335_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.284, 0.427], "wrong_answers": [[0.789, 1.183], [0.61, 0.914], [0.768, 1.153], [-0.217, -0.325]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_336_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_336_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.249, 0.373], "wrong_answers": [[-0.722, -1.083], [0.54, 0.809], [0.8, 1.199], [0.722, 1.083]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_336_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_336_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.302, 0.453], "wrong_answers": [[-0.344, -0.516], [0.706, 1.058], [0.048, 0.072], [0.789, 1.184]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_339_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_339_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.249, 0.373], "wrong_answers": [[-0.345, -0.518], [-0.168, -0.252], [0.476, 0.714], [0.671, 1.007]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_343_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_343_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.427, 0.64], "wrong_answers": [[0.066, 0.099], [0.148, 0.221], [1.033, 1.549], [1.265, 1.897]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_343_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_343_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.267, 0.4], "wrong_answers": [[0.423, 0.635], [-0.169, -0.253], [0.615, 0.923], [0.486, 0.729]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_344_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_344_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.231, 0.347], "wrong_answers": [[-0.034, -0.051], [0.455, 0.683], [0.785, 1.177], [0.889, 1.333]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_345_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_345_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.284, 0.427], "wrong_answers": [[0.622, 0.932], [0.037, 0.055], [0.802, 1.204], [0.504, 0.755]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_349_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_349_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.373, 0.56], "wrong_answers": [[0.13, 0.195], [-0.305, -0.457], [1.033, 1.549], [0.653, 0.98]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_349_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_349_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.178, 0.267], "wrong_answers": [[-0.195, -0.292], [0.392, 0.588], [0.435, 0.653], [-0.328, -0.492]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_350_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_350_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.302, 0.453], "wrong_answers": [[0.17, 0.256], [0.059, 0.088], [0.075, 0.113], [0.846, 1.269]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_350_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_350_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.267, 0.4], "wrong_answers": [[0.404, 0.607], [-0.01, -0.015], [0.658, 0.987], [-0.22, -0.33]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_355_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_355_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.356, 0.533], "wrong_answers": [[0.891, 1.337], [0.136, 0.204], [0.66, 0.99], [1.17, 1.754]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_355_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_355_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.516, 0.773], "wrong_answers": [[0.129, 0.194], [1.261, 1.891], [0.17, 0.254], [0.19, 0.284]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_355_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_355_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.213, 0.32], "wrong_answers": [[-0.382, -0.573], [0.501, 0.752], [0.596, 0.895], [0.051, 0.076]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_355_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_355_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.356, 0.533], "wrong_answers": [[0.553, 0.83], [0.578, 0.867], [0.628, 0.942], [0.904, 1.357]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_358_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_358_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.409, 0.613], "wrong_answers": [[0.251, 0.376], [0.222, 0.333], [0.926, 1.389], [0.813, 1.219]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_358_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_358_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.302, 0.453], "wrong_answers": [[0.858, 1.288], [0.659, 0.989], [-0.069, -0.103], [0.615, 0.922]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_364_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_364_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.498, 0.747], "wrong_answers": [[0.777, 1.165], [0.285, 0.427], [0.156, 0.234], [0.247, 0.371]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_366_iris.csv_['petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_366_iris.csv_['petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.267, 0.4], "wrong_answers": [[-0.283, -0.424], [0.151, 0.227], [0.072, 0.108], [0.922, 1.383]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_367_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_367_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.391, 0.587], "wrong_answers": [[-0.112, -0.168], [0.806, 1.208], [1.233, 1.85], [0.164, 0.246]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_367_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_367_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.533, 0.8], "wrong_answers": [[1.638, 2.456], [0.321, 0.481], [1.125, 1.688], [1.029, 1.544]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_368_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_368_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.498, 0.747], "wrong_answers": [[-0.169, -0.254], [0.857, 1.286], [0.286, 0.429], [0.937, 1.405]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_368_iris.csv_['petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_368_iris.csv_['petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.284, 0.427], "wrong_answers": [[-0.006, -0.009], [0.45, 0.674], [0.444, 0.667], [0.578, 0.867]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_370_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_370_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.32, 0.48], "wrong_answers": [[1.091, 1.637], [-0.317, -0.475], [0.635, 0.953], [-0.265, -0.398]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_371_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_371_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.178, 0.267], "wrong_answers": [[0.594, 0.891], [0.489, 0.734], [0.098, 0.147], [-0.415, -0.622]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_374_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_374_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.409, 0.613], "wrong_answers": [[1.065, 1.598], [0.798, 1.197], [0.744, 1.116], [0.866, 1.299]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_374_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_374_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.284, 0.427], "wrong_answers": [[-0.266, -0.399], [0.804, 1.206], [0.7, 1.049], [0.873, 1.309]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_375_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_375_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.32, 0.48], "wrong_answers": [[0.026, 0.039], [0.054, 0.081], [-0.289, -0.434], [0.632, 0.948]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_376_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_376_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.178, 0.267], "wrong_answers": [[-0.72, -1.08], [0.037, 0.055], [0.915, 1.373], [0.958, 1.437]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_378_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_378_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.498, 0.747], "wrong_answers": [[0.944, 1.416], [0.884, 1.326], [0.029, 0.043], [-0.182, -0.272]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_379_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_379_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.284, 0.427], "wrong_answers": [[0.506, 0.758], [0.145, 0.218], [-0.031, -0.047], [0.16, 0.241]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_383_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_383_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.391, 0.587], "wrong_answers": [[0.14, 0.209], [0.226, 0.339], [-0.374, -0.562], [0.129, 0.193]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_386_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_386_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.284, 0.427], "wrong_answers": [[0.188, 0.282], [0.96, 1.44], [-0.368, -0.551], [0.661, 0.991]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_394_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_394_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.356, 0.533], "wrong_answers": [[0.837, 1.256], [0.711, 1.067], [-0.219, -0.328], [-0.164, -0.246]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_394_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_394_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.267, 0.4], "wrong_answers": [[0.594, 0.891], [-0.117, -0.176], [0.407, 0.611], [-0.235, -0.352]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_400_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_400_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.391, 0.587], "wrong_answers": [[0.138, 0.206], [0.675, 1.012], [0.846, 1.269], [0.625, 0.937]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_402_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_402_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.32, 0.48], "wrong_answers": [[0.612, 0.918], [0.738, 1.107], [0.083, 0.124], [0.144, 0.216]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_406_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_406_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.213, 0.32], "wrong_answers": [[0.543, 0.814], [-0.269, -0.403], [-0.276, -0.414], [0.525, 0.787]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_409_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_409_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.231, 0.347], "wrong_answers": [[0.744, 1.116], [0.614, 0.921], [0.558, 0.837], [0.081, 0.122]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_410_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_410_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.302, 0.453], "wrong_answers": [[-0.155, -0.233], [0.717, 1.075], [-0.284, -0.425], [-0.331, -0.496]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_410_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_410_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.498, 0.747], "wrong_answers": [[0.966, 1.45], [0.845, 1.267], [1.481, 2.221], [-0.197, -0.295]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_415_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_415_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.32, 0.48], "wrong_answers": [[0.572, 0.858], [1.304, 1.956], [1.067, 1.6], [0.496, 0.744]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_415_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_415_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.178, 0.267], "wrong_answers": [[-0.117, -0.176], [0.097, 0.145], [0.568, 0.851], [0.678, 1.017]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_416_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_416_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.231, 0.347], "wrong_answers": [[-0.051, -0.076], [-0.424, -0.636], [-0.362, -0.543], [0.352, 0.528]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_417_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_417_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.267, 0.4], "wrong_answers": [[-0.029, -0.043], [0.897, 1.345], [0.566, 0.849], [0.735, 1.102]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_419_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_419_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.391, 0.587], "wrong_answers": [[-0.331, -0.496], [0.156, 0.234], [0.218, 0.327], [0.651, 0.976]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_420_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_420_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.284, 0.427], "wrong_answers": [[0.865, 1.298], [0.156, 0.234], [0.967, 1.451], [-0.011, -0.016]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_421_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_421_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.213, 0.32], "wrong_answers": [[-0.215, -0.323], [0.359, 0.538], [0.008, 0.012], [0.455, 0.682]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_424_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_424_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.48, 0.72], "wrong_answers": [[1.025, 1.537], [0.287, 0.431], [1.001, 1.501], [0.167, 0.251]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_425_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_425_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.267, 0.4], "wrong_answers": [[-0.119, -0.178], [0.002, 0.003], [-0.057, -0.085], [-0.054, -0.081]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_430_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_430_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.32, 0.48], "wrong_answers": [[0.682, 1.023], [0.559, 0.838], [-0.166, -0.249], [0.657, 0.986]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_430_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_430_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.409, 0.613], "wrong_answers": [[0.178, 0.267], [1.285, 1.928], [-0.291, -0.436], [0.718, 1.077]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_434_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_434_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.284, 0.427], "wrong_answers": [[0.826, 1.239], [0.709, 1.063], [0.782, 1.173], [0.735, 1.103]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_438_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_438_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.516, 0.773], "wrong_answers": [[0.321, 0.481], [0.921, 1.381], [0.786, 1.179], [0.196, 0.293]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_438_iris.csv_['petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_438_iris.csv_['petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.338, 0.507], "wrong_answers": [[-0.297, -0.446], [-0.295, -0.442], [-0.084, -0.126], [0.569, 0.854]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_442_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_442_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.356, 0.533], "wrong_answers": [[1.089, 1.634], [1.083, 1.624], [0.925, 1.388], [1.016, 1.524]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_446_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_446_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.249, 0.373], "wrong_answers": [[0.093, 0.139], [1.37, 2.055], [0.378, 0.567], [0.545, 0.817]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_446_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_446_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.302, 0.453], "wrong_answers": [[0.035, 0.052], [-0.135, -0.203], [0.517, 0.776], [-0.491, -0.736]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_447_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_447_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.32, 0.48], "wrong_answers": [[-0.056, -0.084], [-0.031, -0.046], [0.635, 0.952], [0.481, 0.721]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_447_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_447_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.231, 0.347], "wrong_answers": [[0.676, 1.014], [0.837, 1.255], [0.025, 0.037], [0.885, 1.327]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_451_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_451_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.213, 0.32], "wrong_answers": [[0.696, 1.044], [0.64, 0.96], [-0.081, -0.122], [0.578, 0.867]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_452_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_452_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.391, 0.587], "wrong_answers": [[-0.017, -0.025], [0.672, 1.008], [0.642, 0.963], [-0.092, -0.138]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_463_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_463_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.356, 0.533], "wrong_answers": [[-0.005, -0.007], [0.063, 0.094], [0.61, 0.915], [0.704, 1.056]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_464_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_464_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.284, 0.427], "wrong_answers": [[-0.479, -0.719], [-0.027, -0.04], [0.045, 0.067], [0.89, 1.335]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_466_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_466_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.338, 0.507], "wrong_answers": [[0.565, 0.847], [0.678, 1.017], [0.829, 1.243], [0.899, 1.348]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_474_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_474_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.338, 0.507], "wrong_answers": [[-0.236, -0.354], [1.069, 1.604], [1.083, 1.625], [-0.215, -0.322]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_475_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_475_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.267, 0.4], "wrong_answers": [[1.067, 1.601], [0.787, 1.18], [0.497, 0.745], [0.49, 0.735]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_475_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_475_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.302, 0.453], "wrong_answers": [[0.632, 0.948], [1.152, 1.729], [-0.218, -0.327], [1.198, 1.797]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_478_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_478_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.533, 0.8], "wrong_answers": [[1.406, 2.108], [1.195, 1.792], [1.162, 1.743], [0.977, 1.465]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_481_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_481_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.391, 0.587], "wrong_answers": [[0.152, 0.228], [0.59, 0.885], [-0.218, -0.327], [0.177, 0.266]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_482_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_482_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.373, 0.56], "wrong_answers": [[1.289, 1.934], [0.892, 1.338], [0.933, 1.4], [0.614, 0.92]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_483_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_483_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.231, 0.347], "wrong_answers": [[-0.063, -0.095], [0.557, 0.835], [0.349, 0.524], [0.639, 0.959]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_484_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_484_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.196, 0.293], "wrong_answers": [[-0.292, -0.437], [0.371, 0.557], [0.67, 1.004], [0.705, 1.057]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_485_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_485_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.444, 0.667], "wrong_answers": [[1.091, 1.636], [0.238, 0.357], [0.883, 1.324], [1.158, 1.738]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_487_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_487_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.338, 0.507], "wrong_answers": [[0.204, 0.306], [0.592, 0.889], [-0.254, -0.381], [0.562, 0.843]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_491_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_491_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.356, 0.533], "wrong_answers": [[-0.251, -0.377], [0.845, 1.267], [0.647, 0.97], [-0.124, -0.186]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_492_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_492_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.356, 0.533], "wrong_answers": [[0.764, 1.147], [-0.269, -0.403], [0.955, 1.433], [-0.188, -0.283]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_496_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_496_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.444, 0.667], "wrong_answers": [[1.484, 2.225], [0.804, 1.206], [0.891, 1.336], [0.672, 1.008]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_502_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_502_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.604, 0.907], "wrong_answers": [[1.155, 1.732], [1.044, 1.565], [0.987, 1.481], [0.944, 1.416]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_503_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_503_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.569, 0.853], "wrong_answers": [[0.904, 1.356], [1.26, 1.89], [0.266, 0.399], [1.198, 1.798]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_506_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_506_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.373, 0.56], "wrong_answers": [[0.856, 1.284], [0.768, 1.151], [0.609, 0.913], [0.127, 0.191]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_507_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_507_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.391, 0.587], "wrong_answers": [[0.225, 0.337], [0.097, 0.146], [0.856, 1.285], [0.244, 0.366]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_508_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_508_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.284, 0.427], "wrong_answers": [[0.681, 1.022], [-0.146, -0.22], [0.435, 0.653], [0.534, 0.801]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_512_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_512_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.409, 0.613], "wrong_answers": [[0.705, 1.058], [0.689, 1.034], [1.135, 1.702], [0.682, 1.024]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_513_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_513_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.32, 0.48], "wrong_answers": [[0.517, 0.775], [0.802, 1.203], [0.577, 0.866], [0.638, 0.956]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_515_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_515_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.391, 0.587], "wrong_answers": [[0.065, 0.098], [0.94, 1.411], [0.783, 1.175], [-0.231, -0.347]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_517_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_517_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.356, 0.533], "wrong_answers": [[0.536, 0.804], [0.596, 0.894], [0.54, 0.81], [0.754, 1.131]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_518_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_518_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.427, 0.64], "wrong_answers": [[0.806, 1.21], [0.706, 1.06], [0.72, 1.081], [0.127, 0.19]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_519_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_519_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.48, 0.72], "wrong_answers": [[0.132, 0.197], [0.828, 1.241], [-0.083, -0.125], [0.944, 1.416]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_519_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_519_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.32, 0.48], "wrong_answers": [[-0.255, -0.382], [0.547, 0.82], [0.948, 1.422], [0.105, 0.158]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_522_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_522_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.533, 0.8], "wrong_answers": [[1.411, 2.117], [1.524, 2.286], [0.238, 0.357], [0.251, 0.376]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_522_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_522_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.32, 0.48], "wrong_answers": [[0.055, 0.082], [-0.209, -0.313], [-0.02, -0.031], [0.859, 1.289]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_523_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_523_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.462, 0.693], "wrong_answers": [[0.215, 0.323], [-0.237, -0.355], [0.976, 1.465], [0.949, 1.424]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_525_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_525_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.427, 0.64], "wrong_answers": [[-0.085, -0.127], [1.031, 1.547], [0.671, 1.007], [0.274, 0.411]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_527_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_527_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.391, 0.587], "wrong_answers": [[0.165, 0.247], [0.242, 0.364], [0.046, 0.07], [0.232, 0.349]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_528_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_528_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.267, 0.4], "wrong_answers": [[0.8, 1.201], [0.635, 0.952], [0.089, 0.133], [0.453, 0.68]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_529_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_529_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.373, 0.56], "wrong_answers": [[0.815, 1.223], [0.714, 1.071], [0.192, 0.288], [0.22, 0.33]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_531_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_531_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.338, 0.507], "wrong_answers": [[-0.2, -0.3], [1.319, 1.978], [0.806, 1.208], [0.534, 0.801]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_533_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_533_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.231, 0.347], "wrong_answers": [[0.683, 1.025], [-0.118, -0.177], [1.286, 1.93], [-0.419, -0.629]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_537_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_537_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.267, 0.4], "wrong_answers": [[0.635, 0.953], [0.418, 0.627], [-0.084, -0.126], [-0.418, -0.627]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_541_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_541_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.231, 0.347], "wrong_answers": [[-0.43, -0.645], [0.352, 0.528], [0.5, 0.75], [0.553, 0.83]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_545_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_545_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.32, 0.48], "wrong_answers": [[0.792, 1.188], [0.602, 0.903], [1.074, 1.611], [0.487, 0.73]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_548_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_548_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.231, 0.347], "wrong_answers": [[0.576, 0.864], [0.858, 1.288], [0.109, 0.163], [0.368, 0.553]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_549_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_549_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.338, 0.507], "wrong_answers": [[0.583, 0.874], [-0.431, -0.647], [-0.0, -0.001], [0.524, 0.787]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_553_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_553_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.249, 0.373], "wrong_answers": [[0.962, 1.443], [0.421, 0.632], [0.42, 0.63], [0.674, 1.011]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_553_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_553_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.249, 0.373], "wrong_answers": [[0.146, 0.219], [1.036, 1.554], [0.094, 0.141], [0.407, 0.61]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_555_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_555_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.196, 0.293], "wrong_answers": [[-0.397, -0.596], [0.765, 1.148], [-0.268, -0.403], [0.535, 0.802]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_556_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_556_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.444, 0.667], "wrong_answers": [[-0.207, -0.31], [0.808, 1.211], [0.783, 1.175], [0.199, 0.299]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_557_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_557_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.533, 0.8], "wrong_answers": [[0.16, 0.24], [0.1, 0.15], [0.245, 0.367], [0.932, 1.398]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_558_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_558_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.373, 0.56], "wrong_answers": [[0.014, 0.022], [-0.095, -0.143], [0.602, 0.903], [0.173, 0.259]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_559_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_559_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.302, 0.453], "wrong_answers": [[0.876, 1.313], [0.193, 0.29], [1.14, 1.71], [-0.556, -0.834]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_560_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_560_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.462, 0.693], "wrong_answers": [[0.784, 1.175], [0.716, 1.075], [0.999, 1.498], [0.853, 1.28]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_562_iris.csv_['petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_562_iris.csv_['petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.196, 0.293], "wrong_answers": [[0.371, 0.556], [-0.34, -0.511], [0.548, 0.822], [-0.166, -0.248]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_564_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_564_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.373, 0.56], "wrong_answers": [[0.171, 0.257], [0.969, 1.454], [0.917, 1.376], [0.015, 0.023]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_567_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_567_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.284, 0.427], "wrong_answers": [[0.039, 0.058], [0.152, 0.228], [0.06, 0.09], [0.066, 0.099]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_570_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_570_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.231, 0.347], "wrong_answers": [[0.127, 0.19], [0.705, 1.058], [0.419, 0.628], [0.409, 0.613]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_571_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_571_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.462, 0.693], "wrong_answers": [[-0.134, -0.201], [0.142, 0.213], [0.204, 0.306], [1.457, 2.185]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_573_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_573_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.373, 0.56], "wrong_answers": [[0.894, 1.341], [0.797, 1.196], [0.673, 1.009], [1.42, 2.13]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_579_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_579_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.391, 0.587], "wrong_answers": [[0.83, 1.246], [1.026, 1.538], [1.14, 1.71], [-0.349, -0.523]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_581_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_581_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.462, 0.693], "wrong_answers": [[0.989, 1.484], [1.089, 1.634], [0.224, 0.336], [-0.574, -0.861]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_583_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_583_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.302, 0.453], "wrong_answers": [[-0.566, -0.849], [0.554, 0.831], [1.101, 1.652], [0.743, 1.114]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_587_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_587_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.338, 0.507], "wrong_answers": [[-0.197, -0.296], [-0.074, -0.111], [0.913, 1.37], [0.528, 0.792]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_588_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_588_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.231, 0.347], "wrong_answers": [[-0.185, -0.278], [1.015, 1.523], [0.481, 0.722], [-0.436, -0.653]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_588_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_588_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.32, 0.48], "wrong_answers": [[0.834, 1.25], [0.015, 0.023], [-0.079, -0.119], [-0.242, -0.364]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_590_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_590_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.373, 0.56], "wrong_answers": [[1.802, 2.703], [1.162, 1.744], [0.216, 0.325], [-0.773, -1.159]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_591_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_591_iris.csv_['sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.356, 0.533], "wrong_answers": [[0.136, 0.203], [0.236, 0.355], [0.617, 0.926], [0.717, 1.076]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_592_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_592_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.338, 0.507], "wrong_answers": [[-0.149, -0.224], [-0.362, -0.543], [0.759, 1.139], [0.718, 1.077]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_600_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_600_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.427, 0.64], "wrong_answers": [[-0.228, -0.342], [0.904, 1.355], [0.822, 1.233], [-0.154, -0.231]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_601_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_601_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.338, 0.507], "wrong_answers": [[1.122, 1.683], [0.136, 0.204], [1.082, 1.624], [0.697, 1.046]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_602_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_602_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.498, 0.747], "wrong_answers": [[0.188, 0.282], [0.771, 1.156], [-0.126, -0.188], [0.324, 0.486]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_604_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_604_iris.csv_['petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.444, 0.667], "wrong_answers": [[0.753, 1.13], [-0.278, -0.418], [0.868, 1.302], [0.049, 0.074]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_605_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_605_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.302, 0.453], "wrong_answers": [[0.62, 0.929], [0.539, 0.808], [-0.253, -0.38], [-0.306, -0.459]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_607_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_607_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.338, 0.507], "wrong_answers": [[0.804, 1.206], [0.77, 1.155], [0.543, 0.815], [-0.192, -0.288]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_608_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_608_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.178, 0.267], "wrong_answers": [[0.469, 0.704], [0.772, 1.157], [-0.095, -0.143], [-0.533, -0.8]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_609_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_609_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.391, 0.587], "wrong_answers": [[0.195, 0.293], [0.69, 1.035], [0.809, 1.214], [0.637, 0.956]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_612_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_612_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.338, 0.507], "wrong_answers": [[0.811, 1.217], [0.527, 0.79], [0.109, 0.164], [0.083, 0.124]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_616_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_616_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.32, 0.48], "wrong_answers": [[0.866, 1.299], [-0.722, -1.083], [1.065, 1.597], [0.648, 0.972]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_617_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_617_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.356, 0.533], "wrong_answers": [[0.845, 1.268], [-0.198, -0.298], [0.118, 0.177], [0.8, 1.2]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_620_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_620_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.356, 0.533], "wrong_answers": [[0.17, 0.256], [1.018, 1.527], [0.607, 0.911], [-0.024, -0.036]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_621_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_621_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.462, 0.693], "wrong_answers": [[0.093, 0.139], [0.979, 1.468], [0.74, 1.11], [0.228, 0.342]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_621_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_621_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.356, 0.533], "wrong_answers": [[0.139, 0.208], [0.546, 0.819], [1.094, 1.642], [0.598, 0.898]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_625_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_625_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.267, 0.4], "wrong_answers": [[0.626, 0.939], [0.439, 0.658], [1.237, 1.856], [1.172, 1.758]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_625_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_625_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.231, 0.347], "wrong_answers": [[0.638, 0.957], [-0.071, -0.107], [-0.077, -0.115], [0.551, 0.826]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_627_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_627_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.356, 0.533], "wrong_answers": [[0.552, 0.828], [0.041, 0.062], [-0.305, -0.457], [0.966, 1.449]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_628_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_628_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.231, 0.347], "wrong_answers": [[0.573, 0.86], [-0.309, -0.464], [-0.103, -0.155], [0.031, 0.046]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_630_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_630_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.373, 0.56], "wrong_answers": [[-0.103, -0.154], [-0.271, -0.406], [0.701, 1.052], [-0.225, -0.337]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_630_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_630_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.302, 0.453], "wrong_answers": [[0.5, 0.751], [-0.244, -0.365], [-0.048, -0.072], [-0.025, -0.037]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_632_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_632_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.48, 0.72], "wrong_answers": [[0.169, 0.253], [0.959, 1.439], [0.918, 1.377], [0.94, 1.41]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_632_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_632_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.373, 0.56], "wrong_answers": [[0.17, 0.255], [0.011, 0.016], [0.939, 1.409], [0.903, 1.355]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_632_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_632_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.302, 0.453], "wrong_answers": [[0.065, 0.097], [0.576, 0.864], [0.698, 1.047], [0.74, 1.11]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_637_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_637_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.356, 0.533], "wrong_answers": [[-0.062, -0.093], [0.895, 1.342], [0.623, 0.934], [-0.478, -0.718]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_638_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_638_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.356, 0.533], "wrong_answers": [[-0.348, -0.522], [0.825, 1.237], [0.691, 1.036], [0.603, 0.905]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_640_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_640_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.391, 0.587], "wrong_answers": [[0.602, 0.903], [0.635, 0.952], [1.348, 2.022], [0.599, 0.899]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_640_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_640_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.231, 0.347], "wrong_answers": [[0.865, 1.298], [-0.423, -0.635], [-0.06, -0.091], [0.613, 0.919]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_641_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_641_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.213, 0.32], "wrong_answers": [[-0.085, -0.128], [0.405, 0.607], [0.759, 1.139], [-0.299, -0.449]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_642_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_642_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.356, 0.533], "wrong_answers": [[0.658, 0.988], [0.03, 0.045], [0.547, 0.821], [-0.111, -0.167]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_645_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_645_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.444, 0.667], "wrong_answers": [[-0.098, -0.146], [0.746, 1.119], [0.793, 1.19], [-0.299, -0.449]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_648_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_648_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.373, 0.56], "wrong_answers": [[-0.281, -0.421], [0.185, 0.277], [0.242, 0.363], [0.59, 0.885]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_649_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_649_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.267, 0.4], "wrong_answers": [[-0.229, -0.343], [0.412, 0.617], [1.21, 1.815], [0.686, 1.03]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_649_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_649_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.444, 0.667], "wrong_answers": [[0.154, 0.232], [1.194, 1.792], [-0.167, -0.25], [-0.326, -0.489]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_649_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_649_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.284, 0.427], "wrong_answers": [[0.129, 0.194], [-0.229, -0.343], [0.728, 1.092], [0.656, 0.985]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_650_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_650_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.267, 0.4], "wrong_answers": [[0.029, 0.043], [-0.0, -0.001], [1.851, 2.777], [0.791, 1.186]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_650_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_650_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.48, 0.72], "wrong_answers": [[0.296, 0.445], [1.165, 1.748], [0.983, 1.475], [0.067, 0.101]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_654_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_654_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.338, 0.507], "wrong_answers": [[0.508, 0.762], [0.545, 0.817], [0.937, 1.405], [0.963, 1.444]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_655_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_655_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.302, 0.453], "wrong_answers": [[-0.085, -0.127], [-0.05, -0.075], [0.582, 0.873], [0.178, 0.267]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_656_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_656_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.249, 0.373], "wrong_answers": [[0.838, 1.258], [0.074, 0.111], [-0.191, -0.286], [0.479, 0.719]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_660_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_660_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.231, 0.347], "wrong_answers": [[0.932, 1.398], [0.466, 0.699], [0.689, 1.033], [-0.047, -0.07]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_660_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_660_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.284, 0.427], "wrong_answers": [[0.107, 0.16], [0.016, 0.024], [0.596, 0.894], [0.595, 0.893]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_662_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_662_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.338, 0.507], "wrong_answers": [[0.085, 0.127], [-0.315, -0.473], [0.605, 0.907], [-0.315, -0.473]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_664_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_664_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.267, 0.4], "wrong_answers": [[-0.524, -0.786], [0.176, 0.264], [-0.454, -0.681], [0.738, 1.107]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_667_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_667_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.302, 0.453], "wrong_answers": [[0.009, 0.013], [0.894, 1.341], [0.908, 1.361], [0.516, 0.774]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_668_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_668_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.284, 0.427], "wrong_answers": [[0.492, 0.739], [0.682, 1.023], [0.77, 1.155], [0.474, 0.711]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_672_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_672_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.267, 0.4], "wrong_answers": [[-0.116, -0.174], [0.128, 0.192], [0.769, 1.153], [0.481, 0.721]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_673_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_673_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.249, 0.373], "wrong_answers": [[-0.469, -0.703], [1.124, 1.685], [0.045, 0.067], [0.985, 1.477]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_674_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_674_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.284, 0.427], "wrong_answers": [[-0.115, -0.172], [0.503, 0.754], [0.827, 1.24], [-0.381, -0.571]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_684_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_684_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.533, 0.8], "wrong_answers": [[0.189, 0.284], [1.036, 1.554], [1.015, 1.522], [0.819, 1.229]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_685_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_685_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width', 'petal.length', 'petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.267, 0.4], "wrong_answers": [[0.465, 0.697], [0.128, 0.192], [0.058, 0.087], [0.574, 0.862]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_688_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_688_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.231, 0.347], "wrong_answers": [[0.912, 1.368], [-0.101, -0.151], [0.602, 0.904], [0.833, 1.25]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_689_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_689_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.284, 0.427], "wrong_answers": [[1.679, 2.518], [0.038, 0.056], [-0.007, -0.01], [0.467, 0.7]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_690_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_690_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.267, 0.4], "wrong_answers": [[0.018, 0.027], [0.15, 0.225], [1.069, 1.603], [0.548, 0.822]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_691_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_691_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.356, 0.533], "wrong_answers": [[-0.01, -0.016], [1.085, 1.627], [0.949, 1.424], [-0.26, -0.39]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_692_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_692_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.391, 0.587], "wrong_answers": [[0.027, 0.041], [1.135, 1.703], [0.982, 1.473], [0.102, 0.154]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_693_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_693_iris.csv_['petal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.409, 0.613], "wrong_answers": [[1.054, 1.581], [0.65, 0.975], [-0.579, -0.868], [1.235, 1.853]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_698_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_698_iris.csv_['sepal.length'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.338, 0.507], "wrong_answers": [[0.732, 1.099], [0.933, 1.399], [0.645, 0.968], [-0.232, -0.347]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_699_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_699_iris.csv_['sepal.length', 'sepal.width'].csv"}{"correct_answer": [0.231, 0.347], "wrong_answers": [[-0.34, -0.51], [-0.299, -0.449], [-0.365, -0.547], [1.158, 1.737]], "question": "Please use a Logistic Regression model to classify an iris species as either (Virginica, Setosa, or Versicolor). Evaluate the accuracy of your  model and the f1-score calculated by counting the total true positives, false negatives, and false positives given the training and testing dataset. What is the f1-score of your Logistic Regression model ?", "train_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/train_data/train_data_699_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv", "test_data": "https://github.com/dungkorbit/fpt/blob/master/programming_exercies/exercise/iris/test_data/test_data_699_iris.csv_['sepal.width'].csv"}